[{"answer": "How many great white sharks --", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 7, "question": "How many gun murders were there in Britain?", "qSentId": 6}, {"answer": "Well, we did it as a way to bring attention to the fact that we have all of these foreigners and the Russian government, the official Chinese government.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 34, "question": "Why do you want to deport me?", "qSentId": 33}, {"answer": "Yes, I am finished.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 69, "question": "You finished?", "qSentId": 68}, {"answer": "There were about 11,458, and about 74 percent of those were gang related, gang bangers shooting each other.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 87, "question": "Do you know?", "qSentId": 86}, {"answer": "How many great white sharks --", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 96, "question": "How many gun murders were there in Britain last year?", "qSentId": 95}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 99, "question": "kill people every year but they're scared to swim?", "qSentId": 98}, {"answer": "A very low amount and I already went over those statistics.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 101, "question": "How many gun murders were there in Britain?", "qSentId": 100}, {"answer": "That was only a few hundred.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 103, "question": "How many, do you know?", "qSentId": 102}, {"answer": "I actually, actually did pull up the statistics.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 106, "question": "How many gun murders?", "qSentId": 105}, {"answer": "Why don't you tell folks -- yes, you fled here.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 133, "question": "I fled here?", "qSentId": 132}, {"answer": "Answer this question.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 135, "question": "Why don't you go back and face the charges with the hacking scandal?", "qSentId": 134}, {"answer": "How many --", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 138, "question": "Why did you get fired from \"The Daily Mirror\" for putting on fake stories?", "qSentId": 137}, {"answer": "No, I don't.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 153, "question": "Do you know the answer?", "qSentId": 152}, {"answer": "Hey.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 162, "question": "Do you understand the difference between 11,000 and 35?", "qSentId": 161}, {"answer": "Do you understand --", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 170, "question": "Do you understand the difference?", "qSentId": 169}, {"answer": "They know your script.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 174, "question": "-- and 11,000?", "qSentId": 173}, {"answer": "Well --", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 180, "question": "You can pull those numbers up, OK?", "qSentId": 179}, {"answer": "M-4 AR-15 variant.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 185, "question": "Which weapon was predominantly used in the Aurora movie theater shooting?", "qSentId": 184}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 193, "question": "Do you know that?", "qSentId": 192}, {"answer": "Let me ask you a second question.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 207, "question": "Are we going to -- listen, why do you have the pilots have firearms?", "qSentId": 206}, {"answer": "I understand that people who are mentally ill on all the serotonin reuptake inhibitors --", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 215, "question": "Do you know which weapon was used in the Oregon shopping mall mass shooting recently?", "qSentId": 214}, {"answer": "Listen.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 227, "question": "Do you know what the weapon used was?", "qSentId": 226}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 242, "question": "OK?", "qSentId": 241}, {"answer": "Alex.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 280, "question": "Do you have a bodyguard?", "qSentId": 279}, {"answer": "I don't have a bodyguard.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 282, "question": "Why do you have bodyguards?", "qSentId": 281}, {"answer": "Let me ask you this question.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 286, "question": "Don't you want to protect your wife from hoodlums or you want to call the police?", "qSentId": 285}, {"answer": "Don't be talking over me.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 293, "question": "-- to try and take Mr. And Mrs. America's guns?", "qSentId": 292}, {"answer": "I have already gone over that and already answered it for you.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 310, "question": "What was the weapon used at Sandy Hook?", "qSentId": 309}, {"answer": "It's a 223 M-4.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 315, "question": "What was the weapon?", "qSentId": 314}, {"answer": "People wouldn't go swimming because of the movie \"Jaws\" even though great white sharks kill five people a year.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "Are you seeing a pattern?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "Why -- Alex. I don't --", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 336, "question": "Why is the government arguing [inaudible] against this?", "qSentId": 335}, {"answer": "Alex.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 338, "question": "ONES: What about \"Fast and Furious\"?", "qSentId": 337}, {"answer": "Calm down, Alex.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 340, "question": "Why did our government ship guns to Mexico?", "qSentId": 339}, {"answer": "Let's have a debate.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 342, "question": "To blame the Second Amendment?", "qSentId": 341}, {"answer": "Alex, I get accused --", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 344, "question": "A false flag?", "qSentId": 343}, {"answer": "I get accused --", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 346, "question": "To blame the Second Amendment?", "qSentId": 345}, {"answer": "Alex. Alex. I get accused when I get you guys on of talking over you, of being rude.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 348, "question": "Why did they blow up buildings down the street here in New York?", "qSentId": 347}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 350, "question": "I'm trying to be civil, all right?", "qSentId": 349}, {"answer": "Go commit suicide by killing a bunch of kids and here's the gun to use --", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 367, "question": "Alex, why do people need them?", "qSentId": 366}, {"answer": "They need them to protect us from the number one killer in history.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 371, "question": "Why do people need them?", "qSentId": 370}, {"answer": "Statistically, where there's more guns there's lower crime.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 380, "question": "-- therefore have an AR-15 if they want one?", "qSentId": 379}, {"answer": "Stick to the subject.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 408, "question": "Why don't you want to get rid of drugs, because they're half your sponsors?", "qSentId": 407}, {"answer": "Oh I absolutely know.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 465, "question": "Who do you believe was behind 9/11?", "qSentId": 464}, {"answer": "I have the proof.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 469, "question": "But who do you believe was behind it?", "qSentId": 468}, {"answer": "They announced they blew up the towers on CBS Radio.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 472, "question": "Who, who, Alex?", "qSentId": 471}, {"answer": "Criminal elements of the military industrial complex, the same ones that staged Gulf of Tonkin, the same ones that staged operation, the mass shootings, Operation Gladio.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 477, "question": "Alex, who do you believe -- Alex, who do you believe was behind it, the American government?", "qSentId": 476}, {"answer": "I mean that even mainstream news reported that the hijackers were ordered to be allowed into the United States.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 482, "question": "Alex. Alex. Do you mean that President Bush and his administration were behind 9/11?", "qSentId": 481}, {"answer": "The government -- Hitler fired bombs and turned rash tag, Piers, to bring in martial law in Germany, April 27th, 1933.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 491, "question": "But is that what you believe?", "qSentId": 490}, {"answer": "I probably own more than 50 firearms.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 495, "question": "How many guns do you own?", "qSentId": 494}, {"answer": "It was disheartening, I think, you know I think just to see the anger there.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 521, "question": "What did you feel?", "qSentId": 520}, {"answer": "When our during the aftermath of ObamaCare when there were -- the president was being held in effigy and these kinds of threatening comments of people like the man you just had on were blocking members of Congress from being able to go and vote, you may recall of that, --", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 531, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 530}, {"answer": "Well, as I said, I think that the lack of discourse -- so that that is really what's offensive in our country where we should be able to debate our problems without impugning the integrity of the people who have positions.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 573, "question": "Are you surprised that following the assassinations of John F. Kennedy, of Bobby Kennedy that we are in a position in America now where these kind of lawless mass shootings are happening with regularity and no one is doing much about it?", "qSentId": 572}, {"answer": "Well, I thought maybe we could help you sell some more newspapers.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 605, "question": "Why did you agree to come back?", "qSentId": 604}, {"answer": "Increase your viewership.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 607, "question": "More newspapers?", "qSentId": 606}, {"answer": "I'm sorry, yes, of course.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 611, "question": "You're aware of that?", "qSentId": 610}, {"answer": "That the discussion has not been going anywhere that we can tell in a productive way.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 613, "question": "If you were at the meeting with the Vice President Biden, with the NRA and Wal-Mart and others, what would you be saying?", "qSentId": 612}, {"answer": "RATT: You certainly would want to encourage people who are qualified to carry a concealed firearm to be able to do so in a school zone.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 617, "question": "Right, so your solution if you were there in that meeting would be to arm every school, every church, every hospital, everywhere that members of the public can be?", "qSentId": 616}, {"answer": "They're looking for -- it would seem in their sick minds to see if they can out-do the Virginia Tech slaughter, or some other thing that might be in their perverted minds.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 629, "question": "So why on earth would the fact that it's a gun free zone make any difference to them?", "qSentId": 628}, {"answer": "But you know there were armed security people at Virginia Tech.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 631, "question": "So why should we give them a neon sign that says well, see if you can do better than the last guy over here?", "qSentId": 630}, {"answer": "Especially if you're telling the potential victim you can't be armed.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 644, "question": "My point to you, Mr. Pratt, is that even where you have a mass of well trained people and a mass of firearms, you can still have massacres, you'd accept that?", "qSentId": 643}, {"answer": "While the general was busy defending the country much of the time outside of the country, understandably he may not have noticed the Korean merchants who used an -- not one, but many AR-15 rifles with large magazines to defend themselves --", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 661, "question": "Why do you know more about the impact and capability of the assault weapon than General McChrystal?", "qSentId": 660}, {"answer": "-- against the mobs -- during the Los Angeles riots.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 663, "question": "When was that, Mr. Pratt?", "qSentId": 662}, {"answer": "That was some, what, 20 years ago.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 665, "question": "When was that?", "qSentId": 664}, {"answer": "We're able -- let me finish my point if you would.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 668, "question": "Did you know how long ago that was, Mr. Pratt?", "qSentId": 667}, {"answer": "Well, because the general and his troops are not going to be there to protect the average American, the military nor the police after social order implodes, after a hurricane, after an earthquake, during riots.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 687, "question": "Why do you feel so strongly that civilians, despite what we just heard from a leading general, should still be able to have access to these killing machines?", "qSentId": 686}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, according to your investigature (ph) of the constabulary, the data that you're using for the murder rate in England is a sham.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 715, "question": "Why do you still persist in trying to persuade Americans that the complete opposite is true?", "qSentId": 714}, {"answer": "Go tell the Constabulary of Britain that they are lying.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 729, "question": "How long do you think it takes the police or a pathologist to count 50 bodies a year?", "qSentId": 728}, {"answer": "That's exactly what your own Constabulary is saying.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 733, "question": "That's what you're saying?", "qSentId": 732}, {"answer": "Nine hundred seventy, and you have a violent crime rate that is the fourth highest in any country in the world.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 748, "question": "Mr. Pratt, you are stating -- you are telling me on CNN we had how many gun murders last year?", "qSentId": 747}, {"answer": "Well, it seemed that you had improved your demeanor quite a bit from my own experience with you, and I congratulate you for maintaining it during that whole interview.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 779, "question": "What did you make of Mr. Jones' performance on the interview?", "qSentId": 778}, {"answer": "That's what our founders believed.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 782, "question": "Do you believe that?", "qSentId": 781}, {"answer": "That's not for me to decide.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 792, "question": "How many guns do you want in America, Mr. Pratt?", "qSentId": 791}, {"answer": "Every American should be able to get an AR-15.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 795, "question": "Do you think every American should have an AR-15?", "qSentId": 794}, {"answer": "Well, he's not going to do it by legislative, in my opinion.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 800, "question": "What are you going to do if President Obama wins his battle and brings in new stricter gun control legislation?", "qSentId": 799}, {"answer": "Well, he -- President Obama hasn't banned the importation of ball and powder yet, which George III did, but that was one of the major contributory elements to our war for independence.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 805, "question": "You're likening President Obama to George III?", "qSentId": 804}, {"answer": "The humanity was being able to do nothing during the massacre.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 814, "question": "Where's the humanity in doing nothing after these massacres?", "qSentId": 813}, {"answer": "You're a good guesser, yes, sir.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 820, "question": "And you'd be happy with that if every school suddenly had people running around with guns, right?", "qSentId": 819}, {"answer": "Well, when people carry a concealed firearm, one doesn't exactly know for sure, and the element of surprise remains with the person carrying concealed, which means that somebody contemplating doing something horrible doesn't know which person or persons might be able to arrest him, to stop him, and that's why our jurisdictions that have easy access to concealed carry firearms enjoy lower murder rates than, say, the gun control Mecca of Chicago, which does better than one murder a day.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 822, "question": "Where are they going to put them?", "qSentId": 821}, {"answer": "More important than the number of murders and it doesn't matter how a murder is committed, so I'm not going to really care about --", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 828, "question": "So I'm going to give you one more chance before we finish to say again how many gun murders you believed were in England and Wales in 2011?", "qSentId": 827}, {"answer": "The data we have seen was 970.", "docId": "130112pmt", "aSentId": 832, "question": "Can you repeat the number of gun murders that you said earlier?", "qSentId": 831}]